// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which is NOT a reason for doing audience profiling?",
    answer: "B. It will help the speaker make an impressive speech.",
    options: [
      "A. It will help the speaker limit the content.",
      "B. It will help the speaker make an impressive speech.",
      "C. It will help the speaker identify the language to be used during the delivery.",
      "D. It will help the speaker discover information to connect with the audience."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What function of a good introduction is evident when a speaker tells a joke or an anecdote or a powerful statement?",
    answer: "B. gain audience attention",
    options: [
      "A. establish credibility",
      "B. gain audience attention",
      "C. preview main idea",
      "D. state the purpose of the speech"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What function of introduction is used when a speaker shows the audience that he is reliable and trustworthy to discuss the topic?",
    answer: "A. establish credibility",
    options: [
      "A. establish credibility",
      "B. gain audience attention",
      "C. preview main idea",
      "D. state the purpose of the speech"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What term denotes the smooth transition of one sentence to another or one paragraph to another?",
    answer: "C. logical organization",
    options: [
      "A. duration",
      "B. grammatical correctness",
      "C. logical organization",
      "D. word choice"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which part of the speech provides a summary of the main points of the speech?",
    answer: "B. conclusion",
    options: [
      "A. body",
      "B. conclusion",
      "C. introduction",
      "D. thesis statement"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which part of the speech reveals the goal of the speech?",
    answer: "D. thesis statement",
    options: [
      "A. body",
      "B. conclusion",
      "C. introduction",
      "D. thesis statement"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which part of the speech uses definitions, concrete examples, and testimonies?",
    answer: "A. body",
    options: [
      "A. body",
      "B. conclusion",
      "C. introduction",
      "D. thesis statement"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which statement is NOT true about the body of the speech?",
    answer: "D. If you have only one point in your speech, it will either be too short, or too complicated for the audience to understand.",
    options: [
      "A. The most common number of key points is five.",
      "B. The body of the speech is the core part of the speech.",
      "C. If you have a long point in your speech, you will need to break that point into multiple points.",
      "D. If you have only one point in your speech, it will either be too short, or too complicated for the audience to understand."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which is NOT true about doing the conclusion?",
    answer: "C. Provide key points of discussion",
    options: [
      "A. Present a summary",
      "B. Repeat the key ideas presented",
      "C. Provide key points of discussion",
      "D. Signal the end of your speech"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What method of speech organization presents a comparison and contrast of two or three points?",
    answer: "C. Comparison and Contrast Order",
    options: [
      "A. Chronological Order",
      "B. Spatial Order",
      "C. Comparison and Contrast Order",
      "D. Problem-Solution Order"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "What method of speech organization involves a discussion of both the cause and effect of an issue?",
    answer: "A. Causal Order",
    options: [
      "A. Causal Order",
      "B. Comparison and Contrast",
      "C. Spatial Order",
      "D. Chronological Order"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "What method of speech organization is like going from one place to another, or from one direction to another?",
    answer: "A. Spatial Order",
    options: [
      "A. Spatial Order",
      "B. Causal Order",
      "C. Chronological Order",
      "D. Categorical Order"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "What method of speech organization presents the idea in time order?",
    answer: "B. Chronological Order",
    options: [
      "A. Causal Order",
      "B. Chronological Order",
      "C. Categorical Order",
      "D. Spatial Order"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Which group shows the appropriate use of words?",
    answer: "C. I, II, V",
    options: [
      "A. I, II, III",
      "B. IV, V, VI",
      "C. I, II, V",
      "D. III, IV, VI"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Which pair can help a writer ensure that words are used correctly?",
    answer: "A. I and III",
    options: [
      "A. I and III",
      "B. II and IV",
      "C. III and V",
      "D. IV and VI"
    ]
  },
];
